I'm going to eat you now! You're going to be nice pumpkin soup!
Hi everyone! Welcome to this video. It's a Halloween outfit inspiration.
So I've been asked if I can do a Halloween video and then Pankriff Store approached me and asked me if I want to team up with them for this occasion.
so here we are um i'm going to show you some outfits i think they're not only suitable for
halloween but also for goth parties as well so i try to take cool outfits and i'll add some
accessories to make it a real look so in germany halloween is not that famous yet as in america
it's getting more and more popular within the last few years and there are more parties every
year, well except for this year, and I think it's way bigger festivity in
America with all the families and children dressing up, going from house to
house, saying trick-or-treat. You barely even have that in Germany. I don't even
know when people rang my bell to trick-or-treat within the last few years.
But on the other hand, to talk about prejudice, my impression I get from
movies and all the TV series from American Halloween is that like people
start dressing up in slutty costumes like devils and schoolgirls and whatever
and I know that's a really small part but yeah that's what I see on I don't
know television all the time that's a bit weird anyway let's start with the
looks I'm going to show you it's going to be three outfits and as I said I
I think without the accessories you can wear all of them to the next clubbing party or golf festival, whatever.
I hope you're going to enjoy them.
This is going to be the second outfit.
But let's start with something Asian inspired.
So this is a kimono with a corset belt
and I had this black and red fan so I added some red accessories like the lips and the shoes
to make it a look and did something funny with my hair I don't know um yeah I think it's cool
it's a bit shiny and some leather leggings this outfit is super comfortable because
this is really flexible here and it's a lot of freedom for the arms and my
layers are comfortable as well. The most uncomfortable thing here are the shoes
because they're like really high shoes but I'm used to them so it's fine.
Although I have to say in Germany Halloween is kind of more horror related
and all the ghost stories and stuff so typically German costumes are more like
vampires or dark stuff not some bright and funny stuff because that's costumes
we use for carnival
All right, so this is the cyberpunk look, so to say.
or if I'm closing the zipper it does remind me a bit of Matrix. Alright that
glue is not working anymore. So these are old live action roleplay
plastics to put on the face. Dead glasses as well. They even have lights. So cool stuff.
I think you can wear that whole outfit to a fetish party if you like to. It's totally appropriate.
And yeah, I spray painted my hair black obviously.
So I'm going to wash it out later on, but it is nice to have a change.
A real quick change.
I'm wearing a corset underneath and
that coat is
lacing in the back so it's kind of size adjustable. I don't know if I would wear
the corset for the whole night out because it's a bit exhausting
but I think this is a cool shiny look and I really like this coat with all the
lacing details and the whole graphic stuff.
All right, here we go.
This one was a bit ninja inspired and I bought the sword from a friend.
So if you really want to go to a party with a katana I recommend this one.
It's a live action roleplay weapon, it doesn't hurt a bit and it's a lot more safer.
outfit is comfortable as well. I paired it with my Fernando Berlin boots because
they're like combat style and I think they would be really handy if I were an
assassin. But yeah this was this video for this year's Halloween. I hope you
liked it. I'm going to collect outfit ideas for next year so if you have
something in mind put it down in the comments and don't forget to subscribe.
See you around, have a nice Halloween! Oh by the way I almost forgot I'm going to
show you the reels I did for Instagram with these outfits so stay with me now!
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!